Guide to the Albertson family papers, 1902-1954, bulk 1940s. M2227
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Albertson family papers
1899-1954
1940s
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Albertson family
Albertson, E. Joe (Elijah Joseph), 1880-1965
Albertson, Larrabee
M & S Rare Books, Inc.
M2227
6.59 Linear Feet (12 boxes)
Biographical / Historical
Elijah Joseph Albertson (known as Joseph or E. Joe) was a teacher in the Philippines and Peru and later worked at the Peekskill Evening Star, where he served as editor and co-publisher for nearly 40 years. Albertson was born in Pennsylvania on September 12, 1880, to Elijah and Ella (Larish) Albertson. He wed Beatrice Larrabee in 1910, and the two had several children, including three sons: J. Donald, Larrabee (also referred to as Lad and Larry), and E. Joe Jr. They settled in Peekskill, New York, in 1924, and E. Joe bought the Star with partner Donald F. Ikeler. Larrabee Albertson (born circa 1915) attended Columbia and the University of Hawaii, and later served as a lieutenant in the Air Force in the 1940s. He was stationed in various places including Hawaii, China, and Tampa. Other family members represented in the collection include E. Joe's siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, and Marguerite, as well as Beatrice's sister Louise. Elijah Joseph Albertson, Sr., died in 1965.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists largely of personal correspondence, mostly the incoming and outgoing correspondence of E. Joe Albertson, Sr. while he was living in the Philippines, and the incoming and outgoing correspondence of Larrabee Albertson while he was living in Mexico and then various other locations while serving in the Air Force. Overall contains more than 1500 letters (with envelopes), as well as postcards, greeting cards, and personal ephemera.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchase; 2017. Accession MSS 2017-145.
Philippines -- Description and travel; Teachers -- Philippines; Albertson, E. Joe (Elijah Joseph), 1880-1965; Albertson, Larrabee; M & S Rare Books, Inc.; Albertson family; United States. Air Force
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Marguerite, 1899-09-1901-08 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Marguerite, 1901-09-1901-11 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Marguerite, 1901-11-1901-12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Marguerite, 1902-01-1902-03 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Marguerite, 1902-03-1902-04 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Marguerite, 1902-05-1902-07 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Marguerite, 1902-08-1902-09 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Marguerite, 1902-10-1902-12 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Letters from Mamma, siblings, and others to E. Joe Albertson, 1901-10-1901-12 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Letters from Mamma, siblings, and others to E. Joe Albertson, 1902-02-1902-03 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Letters from Mamma, siblings, and others to E. Joe Albertson, 1902-04-1902-06 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Letters from Mamma, siblings, and others to E. Joe Albertson, 1902-07-1902-11 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Letters from Mamma, siblings, and others to E. Joe Albertson, 1902-12 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, 1903-01-1903-02 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, 1903-03-1903-05 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, 1903-06-1903-08 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, 1903-09-1903-10 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, 1903-11-1903-12 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Telegrams relating news from the United States (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Letters from Mamma, siblings and others to E. Joe Albertson, 1903-02-1903-07 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Letters from Mamma, siblings and others to E. Joe Albertson, 1903-08-1903-10 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Letters from Mamma, siblings and others to E. Joe Albertson, 1903-11-1903-12 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, 1904-01-1904-03 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, 1904-04-1904-06 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, 1904-07-1904-08 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, 1904-09-1904-10 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, 1904-11-1904-12 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, 1905-01-1905-03 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, 1905-04-1905-05 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, 1905-06 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, 1906-01-1906-06 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Mamma and also to siblings: Chauncey, Atta, Hazel, Charles, Margaret, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Correspondence – Letters to and from family members from each other, 1902-1906 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Letters to Chauncey from friends, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Letters to teacher, Joe, from Manuel Roa and letters about him, 1905-1906 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Ephemera, including notice of President McKinley’s death, The Magic Vine, a Thanksgiving verse, information pertaining the Mandeville House, commencement invitation, money order receipts (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Story: Life of a Fire Department Horse, 1905-06 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Photographs, 1912-05 (Box 4, Frame 10)
- Invitation to Joe from Missus Hagley and Johnson, 1905-06 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Marriage announcement of Lorenzo Albertson and Mary, 1906-01 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Marriage announcement of Marguerite Albertson, 1909-04 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Commencement announcement, Louise Larrabee, 1910-06 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Beatrice, his future wife, 1907-04-1908-12 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Beatrice, his future wife, 1909-09-1909-12 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Beatrice, his future wife, 1910-01 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Beatrice, his future wife, 1910-01-1910-02 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Letters from E. Joe Albertson to Beatrice, his future wife, 1910-02-1910-10 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Letters from Beatrice to E. Joe Albertson, her future husband, 1909-01-1909-04 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Letters from Beatrice to E. Joe Albertson, her future husband, 1909-05 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Letters from Beatrice to E. Joe Albertson, her future husband, 1909-06-1909-10 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Letters from Beatrice to E. Joe Albertson, her future husband, 1909-10-1910-04 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Letters for the bride, Beatrice Larrabee, from the first grade (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Christmas cards, Easter cards and other wishes; Mother’s Lullaby (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Letters to E. Joe from friends, E. Detwiler, and Elizabeth Richart, 1905-1908 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Letter to E. Joe from fellow teacher, 1908-04 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Letters to E. Joe from Atta, 1913 and 1941 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Letters from Sarah to family, 1911-02 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Letter to A. E. Albertson from Caspar Hodgson, 2010-01 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- 6 Letter to E. Joe about receipt of revolver, 1908-11 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Letters to Beatrice, from various people, 1906-1910 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Love letter to “Darling wife”, 1918-02 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Letters from Don and Larrabee, 1920-1921 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Letters to Atta, 1913 and 1925 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Business letters to E. Joe, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- War Trade Board correspondence, 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Letters to Atta from various family members and friends, 1916-1936 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Correspondence of Atta, Ida and Anne Kelly, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Correspondence - Aunt Atta and Larrabee, 1937-1950 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - Aunt Atta and Larrabee, 1944-07 (Flat-box 12)
- Letters to various family members and friends from Atta, 1904-1936 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Letter to Friends from A.C. Raw, 1935-11 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Letter to Mrs. E. Joe from Louise, 1939-10 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Letter to Grandma from B., 1938-08 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Larrabee, son of E. Joe and Beatrice - record of activities, 1931-1945 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Letter to Uncle Chauncey and Dot from Larrabee, 1942-01 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Correspondence between family members, many from “dad”, 1942-12-1943-08 (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
- Letter to Folks from Larrabee (fragile), 1943-08 (Flat-box 12)
- Letters to Folks, some to family or specifically to mom or to dad, from Larrabee, 1941-07-1941-11 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Letters to Folks, some to family or specifically to mom or to dad, from Larrabee, 1941-12 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Letters to Folks, some to family or specifically to mom or to dad, from Larrabee, 1942-01-1942-02 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Letters to Folks, some to family or specifically to mom or to dad, from Larrabee, 1942-02-1942-07 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Letters to Folks, some to family or specifically to mom or to dad, from Larrabee, incomplete dates (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Letters to Folks, some to family or specifically to mom or to dad, from Larrabee, 1944-01-1944-07 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Letters to Folks, some to family or specifically to mom or to dad, from Larrabee, 1944-08-1944-09 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Letters to Folks, some to family or specifically to mom or to dad, from Larrabee, 1944-10-1944-12 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Letters to Folks, some to family or specifically to mom or to dad, from Larrabee, 1945-01-1945-05 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Letters to Folks, some to family or specifically to mom or to dad, from Larrabee, 1945-06-1945-09 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Letters to Folks, some to family or specifically to mom or to dad, from Larrabee, 1952-08 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Letters to Larrabee from Aunt Louise, 1938-1944 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Letters to Aunt Louise from Larrabee, 1938-1944 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Letters to Larrabee from dad, and from dad Phillips, 1938-1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Correspondence of Joe and Beatrice with Mr. and Mrs. Phillips, May and June 1943 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Letters to Larrabee from various people, unidentified (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Letters to Larrabee from Ray, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from G. and Mabel Runyan (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee (Lad) from Grandma, 1938-08 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Ruth Hobson, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Cy (Serrell Hillman), 1938-1940 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Cousin Glenn, 1938-1941 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Sadie Farkoff, 1938-12 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Caryl (Jilli), 1938-12 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Francis Myers, 1939-02 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Gerry, 1939-07 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Emma, 1939-11 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Shirley Thomas, 1939-12 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Dorothy Shipman, 1939-12 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Emmie (?), 1940-02 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee and Don from Anna and Doris, 1940-03 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Isabel and from Dorothy, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Elmer, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Letters to Larrabee from PJ, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Letters to Larrabee from Auntie an Uncle Harold, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Letters to Larrabee from Flavia Scranton, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Letters to Larrabee from Brad Scanton (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Letters to Larrabee fromMona (?), 1940 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Letters to Larrabee fromMarie Shimizu, friend, 1940-09 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Letters to Larrabee from Mike, 1941-04 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Letters to Larrabee from Hugo, 1941-04 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Letters to Larrabee from Henry Meyer, 1941-04 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Letters to Larrabee from DMK, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Letters to Larrabee from Patz (?), 1941-05 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Letters to Larrabee from Sunday school students, 1941-12 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Letters to Larrabee from Aubrey, 1941-1943 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Letters to Larrabee from D., 1942-1943 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Letters to Larrabee from John, 1943-03 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Letters to Larrabee from Jim (James Lounsbury), 1939 and 1943 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Letters to Larrabee from Alfred Reutersham, 1942-07 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Letters to Larrabee from Alfred Reutersham, 1942-07 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Letters to Larrabee from Bill Forest, News Editor WGNY, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- 6 Letters to Larrabee from Reuben, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Letters to Larrabee from A. Withington (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Letters to Larrabee from Elizabeth, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Letters to Larrabee from Aunt Hazel, 1941 and 1944 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Postcard to ? from Hazel, 1941-04 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Letters to Larrabee from James Mackay, the Star, 1954-05 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Various unidentified letters (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Letter to Pop from George, 1944-06 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Letter to Chuck from Terrific Ted n.d. (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Letter to Milly from Jackie, 1942-09 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Letters to Larry “Palsito” from Maria, 1938-1944 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Letters to Larrabee from Anna, 1939-1941 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Letters to Larrabee from Eileen, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Uora, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Ginnie (Virginia), 1940-1943 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Letters to Lad from Lois, 1939-1945 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Letters to Lois from Lad, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - Larry and Lois with folks and Chico, 1942-07-1943-08 (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
- Two recipe cards, one especially good for food ration days, used as support for messages inked on leaves [in flat box 12), 1943-10 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Memo to Larry about birth of daughter, Lari, born 4/4/44 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Letters to Lari from Larry right after birth, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Mom’s baby diary [about Lari], 1945-04 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Letter to Lari from Mama, 1948-01 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Nursery school report for Lari, 1947-06 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Letter to daddy from Lari, 1947-08 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Letter to Lois from Puretia ? and Tuck, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Memo about Christmas gift of $2000 to Larrabee and Lois from dad and mom, 1949-12 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Letter to Louise from Henry M. Snyder & Co. regarding publishing Larrabee’s book, 1938-11 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Requests for letters of recommendation, 1939-1942 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Letters of recommendation for Larrabee, 1942-01 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Reporting memo to Larrabee, 1942-04 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Restricted memo, Larrabee Albertson, 1942-04 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Reassignment of Larrabee Albertson, 1943-06 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter to Larrabee from Don, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter to Lad from Don, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letters to Don from Larrabee and from Lois, 1943-07 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter from E. Joe regarding order of a grill for Larrabee, 1944-07 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter to Miss Larrabee from Louise, 1938-09 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter to family from Louise (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter to folks and letter to Bee and all, 1941-12 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter to family, 1944-03 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter to folks and letter to Bee and all (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Unidentified letters (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Renewal letter of “Mexico” magazine, 1943-08 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Ephemera, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Ephemera, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Map of Hawaii, brochure about Kauai (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Cancelled envelopes, 1900-1931 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Cancelled envelopes, 1940's (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
- Cancelled envelopes, 1950's (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Letters to Larry “Palsito” from Maria, 1938-1944 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Letters to Larrabee from Anna, 1939-1941 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Letters to Larrabee from Eileen, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Uora, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Letters to Larrabee from Ginnie (Virginia), 1940-1943 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Letters to Lad from Lois, 1939-1945 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Letters to Lois from Lad, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - Larry and Lois with folks and Chico, 1942-07-1943-08 (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
- Two recipe cards, one especially good for food ration days, used as support for messages inked on leaves [in flat box 12], 1943-10 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Memo to Larry about birth of daughter, Lari, born 4/4/44 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Letters to Lari from Larry right after birth, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Mom’s baby diary [about Lari], 1945-04 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Letter to Lari from Mama, 1948-01 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Nursery school report for Lari, 1947-06 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Letter to daddy from Lari, 1947-08 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Letter to Lois from Puretia ? and Tuck, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Memo about Christmas gift of $2000 to Larrabee and Lois from dad and mom, 1949-12 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Letter to Louise from Henry M. Snyder & Co. regarding publishing Larrabee’s book, 1938-11 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Requests for letters of recommendation, 1939-1942 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Letters of recommendation for Larrabee, 1942-01 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Reporting memo to Larrabee, 1942-04 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Restricted memo, Larrabee Albertson, 1942-04 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Reassignment of Larrabee Albertson, 1943-06 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter to Larrabee from Don, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter to Lad from Don, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letters to Don from Larrabee and from Lois, 1943-07 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter from E. Joe regarding order of a grill for Larrabee, 1944-07 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter to Miss Larrabee from Louise, 1938-09 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter to family from Louise (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter to folks and letter to Bee and all, 1941-12 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter to family, 1944-03 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Letter to folks and letter to Bee and all (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Unidentified letters (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Renewal letter of “Mexico” magazine, 1943-08 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Ephemera, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Ephemera, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Map of Hawaii, brochure about Kauai (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Cancelled envelopes, 1900-1931 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Cancelled envelopes, 1940's (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
- Cancelled envelopes, 1950's (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Newspaper clippings, announcements, flyers, sent with letters (Flat-box 12)
- Phillippines constabulary supply receipt, 1902-06 (Flat-box 12)
- Letter to folks from Larrabbee and letter to Larrabee from dad, 1943-08 (Flat-box 12)
- Letter to Larrabee from Aunt Atta, 1944-07 (Flat-box 12)
- Letter to Mac from Chico, 1944-06 (Flat-box 12)
- Letters to Mamma and others from E. Joe, 1903-04 (Flat-box 12)
- Letter to Chauncey from E. Joe, 1902-02 (Flat-box 12)
- Letter to Joe from Beatriz, 1906-10 (Flat-box 12)
- Messages penned on tree leaves (from Larrabee to Lois?) (Flat-box 12)